analysistabs.com 2018-06-15

# Privacy Policy - ANALYSISTABS - Innovating Awesome Tools for Data Analysis!

Privacy of our visitors is extremely importance to us. This page outlines the Privacy Policy and types of personal information collected on this website and how it is used.  
  
**Effective Jan 2013:**

#### We may collect the following information:

If you register to our site or subscribe to my RSS Feeds or Email Updates (powered by Feedburner), we ask for contact information such as name and email address. You may opt-out of these communications at any time. Your personal information will never be sold or given to a third party.

This site does not collect any data from visitors, other than standard server logs. The information inside the log files includes type of browser, Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, Internet Service Provider (ISP), Date – time stamp, Referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyse trends, administer the site, track visitor’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information.

However, we use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information  
(not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

#### Cookies:

We use cookies on this website. Cookies are small text files created by a web server, delivered through a web browser, and stored on your computer. They provide a means for websites that you visit to keep track of online patterns and preferences, as well as to identify return visitors. Cookies make the personalization of your web experiences possible, so that you do not need to re-enter your information each time you visit a website. We also serve cookies to help us anonymously track web traffic, as described above.

These advertisers may use cookies which are collected by the advertising companies.  
For more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having  
this information used by these companies, please check the advertisers’ websites for respective privacy policies.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 
  * If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

#### Changes to Our Privacy Policy:

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time, for any reason. We update such changes in this page including effective date. We recommand you to check our Privacy Policy frequently to review and ensure that you are happy with such changes. 

#### Questions?

If you have any questions or concerns about this website Privacy Policy please contact me at **info@analysistabs.com**
